(Amy:)Which word's tripping you up?
Assuage or aItruism?
(Penny:)Both.
(Bernadette:)You'll feel better
by doing something nice for someone.
- Oh, I actually knew that.
- I never doubted you.
(Bernadette:)Every other week,
I serve at a soup kitchen downtown.
(Penny:)Ooh. I can't do that.
(Penny:)If I stand over a steaming pot,
my hair just goes: "Boing!"
- Ah. What else can I do?
- There's Habitat for Humanity.
(Amy:)Building houses for the poor.
I don't have my own house,
I'm gonna build one for someone else?
(Amy:)How about donating
some of your clothes?
Oh, my God, that's perfect, because
I have so many clothes I don't wear.
They're taking up space
I go shopping to buy more.
(Penny:)I have no place to put it.
This would fix that.
- What about helping people?
- And helping people.
- Here's your cocoa.
- Oh.
- HaIf and haIf instead of whole milk?
- Yes.
- Heated to precisely 183 degrees?
(Sheldon:)Seven little marshmallows,
no more, no less?